A Guide to the Charles F. Gillette, Papers, ca. 1880-1985 (bulk 1918-1969)
Library of Virginia
- Client Correspondence and Card File, 1921-1968.
  - Duke, Lee B.- CCN 203 1953 (Box 22, Folder 15)
    Gillette account number: 1154
  - Dunlap, Mrs.M. S.- CCN 206 1948-1949 (Box 22, Folder 16)
    Gillette account number: 912
  - Dunlop, Mrs.John- CCN 204 1952-1965 (Box 22, Folder 17)
    Gillette account number: 478
  - Dunn, Mrs.W. McKee- CCN 205 1953-1956 (Box 22, Folder 18)
    Gillette account number: 218
  - duPont, Mrs.Alfred I.- CCN 207 1946-1954 (Box 22, Folder 19)
    Gillette account number: 680
  - duPont, Mrs.E. Paul- CCN 208 1945-1947 (Box 22, Folder 20)
  - duPont Company, - CCN 1210 1942 (Box 22, Folder 21)
    Gillette account number: 696
  - Duvall, Mrs. S.P.C.- CCN 209 1964 (Box 22, Folder 22)
  - Dwyer, Mrs.Charles A.- CCN 210 1966 (Box 22, Folder 23)
    Gillette account number: 2468
  - E General, 1943-1956 (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - Eagle, Mrs.Henry- CCN 211 1943-1965 (Box 23, Folder 2)
    Gillette account number: 2036
  - Earp, Miss Bertie E.- CCN 212 1958 (Box 23, Folder 3)
    Gillette account number: 2208
  - Earp, Dr.R. E.- CCN 213 1941-1947 (Box 23, Folder 4)
    Gillette account number: 695
  - Earp, Dr.R. E.- CCN 213 1948 (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - Earp, Dr.R. E.- CCN 213 1949-1957 (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - East Carolina College, - CCN 214 1953-1954 (Box 23, Folder 7)
    Gillette account number: 1179
  - East Willow Lawn Corp., - CCN 215 1955 (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - Eastern North Carolina Sanitarium, - CCN 216 1943-1950 (Box 23, Folder 9)
    Gillette account number: 962
  - Eastern North Carolina Sanitarium, - CCN 216 1951 (Box 23, Folder 10)
  - Eastern North Carolina Sanitarium, - CCN 216 1952-1956 (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - Eastern State Hospital - Project No. 704-53, - CCN 217 1962-1963 (Box 24, Folder 2)
    Gillette account number: 2241
  - Eastern State Hospital - Project No. 704-53, - CCN 217 1964 Jan-Jun (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - Eastern State Hospital - Project No. 704-53, - CCN 217 1964 Jly-Dec (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - Eastern State Hospital - Project No. 704-53, - CCN 217 1965 (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - Eastern State Hospital - Project No. 704-35-60, - CCN 217 1962-1965 (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - Eastern State Hospital - Project No. 704-50, - CCN 217 1965-1967 (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - Eastern State Hospital - Dunbar Site, - CCN 217 1958-1960 (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - Eastern State Hospital - Dunbar Site, - CCN 217 1961-1964 (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - Edgerton, N. Edward- CCN 218 1931-1960 (Box 25, Folder 4)
    Gillette account number: 372
  - Edmond, Paul E.- CCN 219 1963-1966 (Box 25, Folder 5)
    Gillette account number: 2374
  - Effinger, Robert C.- CCN 220 1955 (Box 25, Folder 6)
    Gillette account number: 2077
  - Elizabeth River Tunnel Commission, - CCN 221 1951-1956 (Box 25, Folder 7)
    Gillette account number: 1065
  - Emery, Mrs.Audrey- CCN 223 1961-1964 (Box 26, Folder 1)
    Gillette account number: 2324
  - Emmanuel Episcopal Church, - CCN 222 1956-1962 (Box 26, Folder 2)
    Gillette account number: 2013
  - Emory, Mrs.William H.- CCN 224 1953-1965 (Box 26, Folder 3)
    Gillette account number: 1007
  - Epes, Travis, Jr.- CCN 1053 1961 (Box 26, Folder 4)
    Gillette account number: 2331
  - Episcopal High School, - CCN 225 1950-1951 (Box 26, Folder 5)
    Gillette account number: 973
  - Episcopal High School, - CCN 225 1952-1968 (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - Episcopal High School, - CCN 225 n.d. (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - Episcopal Seminary, - CCN 226 1955-1958 (Box 26, Folder 8)
  - Ervinton High School, - CCN 227 1954-1956 (Box 26, Folder 9)
    Gillette account number: 1175
  - Erwin, Mary B.- CCN 228 1947 (Box 26, Folder 10)
  - Etherington, Dr.John L.- CCN 229 1958 (Box 26, Folder 11)
    Gillette account number: 2206
  - Evans, Mrs. E. Hervey- CCN 230 1942 (Box 26, Folder 12)
    Gillette account number: 650
  - F General, 1944-1965 (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - Farley, Ernst W., Jr.- CCN 231 1964 (Box 27, Folder 2)
    Gillette account number: 2405
  - Father Judge Mission Seminary, - CCN 232 1960 (Box 27, Folder 3)
    Gillette account number: 2299
  - Father Judge Mission Seminary, - CCN 232 1961-1963 (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - Faulkner, Waldron- CCN 233 1942-1950 (Box 27, Folder 5)
    Gillette account number: 560
  - Fay, Fred- CCN 234 1962-1964 (Box 27, Folder 6)
    Gillette account number: 2344
  - Ferrum Junior College, - CCN 235 1962-1967 (Box 27, Folder 7)
    Gillette account number: 2364
  - Fillmore, Mrs.William H.- CCN 236 1949 (Box 27, Folder 8)
  - First and Merchants National Bank, Richmond, VA, Willow Lawn Office, - CCN 243 1965 (Box 27, Folder 9)
    Gillette account number: 2447
  - First and Merchants National Bank, Richmond, VA, Westhampton Branch, - CCN 242 1966-1967 (Box 27, Folder 10)
    Gillette account number: 2477
  - First Baptist Church, Hopewell, VA, - CCN 237 n.d. (Box 27, Folder 11)
  - First Baptist Church, Martinsville, VA, - CCN 238 1955-1959 (Box 27, Folder 12)
    Gillette account number: 2130
  - First Baptist Church, Wilson, NC., - CCN 239 1952-1954 (Box 27, Folder 13)
    Gillette account number: 1119
  - First Federal Savings and Loan, Richmond, VA - Patterson Avenue Branch, - CCN 240 1953-1955 (Box 27, Folder 14)
    Gillette account number: 1164
  - First Federal Savings and Loan, Rocky Mount, NC, - CCN 241 1953-1956 (Box 27, Folder 15)
    Gillette account number: 1145
  - First Methodist Church, Wilson, NC, - CCN 244 1956-1957 (Box 27, Folder 16)
    Gillette account number: 2088
  - First National & Savings Bank, - CCN 246 1959 (Box 28, Folder 1)
    Gillette account number: 2284
  - First National Bank, Louisville, KY, - CCN 245 1953-1954 (Box 28, Folder 2)
    Gillette account number: 1166
  - First Presbyterian Church, Durham, NC, - CCN 247 1964 (Box 28, Folder 3)
    Gillette account number: 2408
  - First Presbyterian Church, Richmond, VA, - CCN 248 1959-1966 (Box 28, Folder 4)
    Gillette account number: 1018
  - First Presbyterian Church, Rocky Mount, NC, - CCN 249 1945-1947 (Box 28, Folder 5)
    Gillette account number: 798
  - First Presbyterian Church, Wilson, NC, - CCN 250 1953-1956 (Box 28, Folder 6)
    Gillette account number: 1139
  - Fitchett, Dr. H. F.- CCN 251 1952 (Box 28, Folder 7)
    Gillette account number: 1092
  - Flowers, Mrs.George H.- CCN 252 1943-1967 (Box 28, Folder 8)
    Gillette account number: 2194
  - Forbes, C. Heber- CCN 253 1944-1946 (Box 28, Folder 9)
  - Ford Motor Company, - CCN 254 1951 (Box 28, Folder 10)
  - Forest Lawn Cemetery, - CCN 1082 n.d. (Box 28, Folder 11)
    Gillette account number: 147
  - Fork Union Military Academy, - CCN 255 1949 (Box 28, Folder 12)
    Gillette account number: 948
  - Fort Eustis Dental Clinic, - CCN 1037 n.d. (Box 28, Folder 13)
    Gillette account number: 2372
  - Fountain, Mrs.R. M.- CCN 256 1950 (Box 28, Folder 14)
    Gillette account number: 989
  - Francis N. Sander's Nursing Home, - CCN 257 1960 (Box 28, Folder 15)
    Gillette account number: 2287
  - Franklin, Mrs.W. M.- CCN 259 1958-1960 (Box 28, Folder 16)
    Gillette account number: 2224
  - Franklin Baptist Church, - CCN 258 1959-1960 (Box 28, Folder 17)
    Gillette account number: 2278
  - Franklin, Town of, - CCN 260 1944-1962 (Box 28, Folder 18)
    Gillette account number: 813
  - Fray, J. H.- CCN 261 1957-1958 (Box 28, Folder 19)
    Gillette account number: 2175
  - Freeman Cemetery, - CCN 1161 n.d. (Box 28, Folder 20)
  - Freeman, Mrs.Charles- CCN 262 n.d. (Box 28, Folder 21)
    Gillette account number: 2304
  - Freeman, Dr. Douglas Southall- CCN 263 1942-1953 (Box 28, Folder 22)
    Gillette account number: 619
  - Freeman, Dr. Jere D.- CCN 264 1950 (Box 28, Folder 23)
    Gillette account number: 704
  - Freeman, Philip D.- CCN 265 1945-1947 (Box 28, Folder 24)
  - Fuller-Kinlaw Co., - CCN 266 1956-1957 (Box 28, Folder 25)
  - G General, 1941-1966 (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - Gables Hotel Corporation, - CCN 267 1943-1944 (Box 29, Folder 2)
    Gillette account number: 751
  - Gadsby Tavern, - CCN 1211 1948-1961 (Box 29, Folder 3)
    Gillette account number: 867
  - Gaines, Dr.F. P. (Townhouse)- CCN 1160 1960 (Box 29, Folder 4)
    Gillette account number: 2309
  - Gaines, Dr.Francis P.- CCN 268 1960-1961 (Box 29, Folder 5)
  - Galban, J. S.- CCN 955 1931 (Box 29, Folder 6)
    Gillette account number: 399
  - Garden Club of North Carolina, - CCN 269 1952 (Box 29, Folder 7)
  - Gates, Mrs.H. T., Jr.- CCN 1055 n.d. (Box 29, Folder 8)
    Gillette account number: 2471
  - Gatewood, Dr. E. T.- CCN 270 1958 (Box 29, Folder 9)
    Gillette account number: 2245
  - Gatewood, Mrs. John M, Jr.- CCN 271 1957-1959 (Box 29, Folder 10)
    Gillette account number: 2178
  - Gayle, Joseph Y.- CCN 272 1949-1955 (Box 29, Folder 11)
    Gillette account number: 936
  - Gayle, Dr.R. Finley- CCN 273 1946-1949 (Box 29, Folder 12)
  - Geiger, J. H.- CCN 274 1942-1943 (Box 29, Folder 13)
    Gillette account number: 740
  - Gibb, Mrs. Duncan C.- CCN 277 1954 (Box 29, Folder 14)
  - Gibson, George D.- CCN 278 1945-1967 (Box 29, Folder 15)
    Gillette account number: 822
  - Gifford, Ralph C.- CCN 279 1943-1945 (Box 29, Folder 16)
    Gillette account number: 758
  - Gifford, Ralph C.- CCN 279 1946-1949 (Box 29, Folder 17)
  - Gillette, Charles F. (105 East Cary St.)- CCN 985 n.d. (Box 29, Folder 18)
    Gillette account number: 446
  - Gillette, Col.George W.- CCN 280 1950-1951 (Box 29, Folder 19)
    Gillette account number: 987
  - Gilliam, Frank J.- CCN 275 1942-1945 (Box 29, Folder 20)
    Gillette account number: 537
  - Gilliam, Frank J.- CCN 275 1946-1949 (Box 30, Folder 1)
  - Gilliam, Frank J.- CCN 275 1950-1954 (Box 30, Folder 2)
  - Gilliam, Frank J.- CCN 275 1956-1966 (Box 30, Folder 3)
  - Gilliam, James R., Jr. (Subdivision)- CCN 281 1951-1959 (Box 30, Folder 4)
    Gillette account number: 1047
  - Gilliam, Mrs. McCleur- CCN 282 1955 (Box 30, Folder 5)
  - Ginter Park Baptist Church, - CCN 1103 n.d. (Box 30, Folder 6)
    Gillette account number: 1083
  - Ginter Park Methodist Church, - CCN 283 1951 (Box 30, Folder 7)
    Gillette account number: 1033
  - Glasgow Company, - CCN 284 1955 (Box 30, Folder 8)
    Gillette account number: 2148
  - Godwin, Dr.F. Whitney- CCN 285 1952-1953 (Box 30, Folder 9)
  - Goldner, Dr. J. L.- CCN 286 1954-1955 (Box 30, Folder 10)
    Gillette account number: 2041
  - Goldsboro City Park Memorial, - CCN 287 1954 (Box 30, Folder 11)
  - Goldsboro Hospital, - CCN 289 n.d. (Box 30, Folder 12)
  - Goldsboro Presbyterian Church, - CCN 288 1956-1960 (Box 30, Folder 13)
    Gillette account number: 1056
  - Golsan, Mrs. Ramage- CCN 290 1941-1944 (Box 30, Folder 14)
  - Good, Norman B., Jr.- CCN 291 1964 (Box 30, Folder 15)
    Gillette account number: 2417
  - Goodloe, S. P.- CCN 292 1952-1954 (Box 30, Folder 16)
    Gillette account number: 773
  - Goodridge, H. B.- CCN 293 1942-1945 (Box 30, Folder 17)
  - Gordon, John B.- CCN 294 1952 (Box 30, Folder 18)
  - Gore, Virgil S.- CCN 295 1956 (Box 30, Folder 19)
    Gillette account number: 2105
  - Gorman, Joseph V.- CCN 296 1949 (Box 31, Folder 1)
  - Gottwald, Bruce C.- CCN 297 1963-1965 (Box 31, Folder 2)
    Gillette account number: 2366
  - Gottwald, F. D.- CCN 298 1950-1966 (Box 31, Folder 3)
    Gillette account number: 1162
  - Governor's Mansion, - CCN 299 1954 (Box 31, Folder 4)
    Gillette account number: 2000
  - Governor's Mansion, - CCN 299 1955 (Box 31, Folder 5)
  - Governor's Mansion, - CCN 299 1956-1959 (Box 31, Folder 6)
  - Governor's Mansion, - CCN 299 n.d. (Box 31, Folder 7)
  - Grace and Holy Trinity Episcopal Church, - CCN 1012 n.d. (Box 32, Folder 1)
    Gillette account number: 2396
  - Graham, Ray A.- CCN 300 1961 (Box 32, Folder 2)
    Gillette account number: 2319
  - Grasty, Taylor- CCN 301 1957-1966 (Box 32, Folder 3)
    Gillette account number: 2204
  - Gravely, P. K.- CCN 302 1949 (Box 32, Folder 4)
    Gillette account number: 933
  - Gray, Mrs.Bowman- CCN 303 1951 (Box 32, Folder 5)
    Gillette account number: 1050
  - Gray, Elmon- CCN 304 1965 (Box 32, Folder 6)
    Gillette account number: 2427
  - Gray, Miss Helen- CCN 305 1959-1960 (Box 32, Folder 7)
    Gillette account number: 2280
  - Gray, Horace- CCN 950 1947-1956 (Box 32, Folder 8)
    Gillette account number: 851
  - Gray, Richmond- CCN 306 1963-1967 (Box 32, Folder 9)
    Gillette account number: 2384
  - Green, Oscar, Jr.- CCN 308 1958 (Box 32, Folder 10)
    Gillette account number: 2191
  - Green, Paul- CCN 307 1946-1965 (Box 32, Folder 11)
    Gillette account number: 601
  - Greenfields, Inc., Subdivision, - CCN 309 1955-1958 (Box 32, Folder 12)
    Gillette account number: 2086
  - Greensboro College, - CCN 310 1950 (Box 32, Folder 13)
    Gillette account number: 1021
  - Greenville, NC, Schools, - CCN 311 1955-1957 (Box 32, Folder 14)
  - Gregory, Henry, Jr.- CCN 312 1947-1951 (Box 32, Folder 15)
    Gillette account number: 869
  - Gregory, Henry, Jr.- CCN 312 1952-1953 (Box 32, Folder 16)
  - Groh, Norman- CCN 313 1957-1958 (Box 32, Folder 17)
    Gillette account number: 2187
  - Grymes Memorial School, - CCN 314 1966-1967 (Box 32, Folder 18)
    Gillette account number: 2490
  - Gunn, Mrs. Julian- CCN 315 1942-1943 (Box 32, Folder 19)
    Gillette account number: 722
  - Gunst, Mrs. Edward- CCN 316 1938-1963 (Box 32, Folder 20)
    Gillette account number: 620
  - H General, 1942-1955 (Box 33, Folder 1)
  - H General, 1956-1966 (Box 33, Folder 2)
  - Hadley, Willis D.- CCN 317 1947-1950 (Box 33, Folder 3)
    Gillette account number: 890
  - Hadley, Willis D.- CCN 317 1951-1954 (Box 33, Folder 4)
  - Hagan, John C., Jr.- CCN 318 1951 (Box 33, Folder 5)
    Gillette account number: 1132
  - Hall, Irving F.- CCN 319 1944-1945 (Box 33, Folder 6)
    Gillette account number: 653
  - Hampden Sydney College, - CCN 320 1937-1961 (Box 33, Folder 7)
    Gillette account number: 951
  - Hancock, Dr.Edward H.- CCN 321 1962 (Box 33, Folder 8)
    Gillette account number: 2353
  - Hardy, H. S.- CCN 322 1951-1952 (Box 33, Folder 9)
    Gillette account number: 1076
  - Harles, Harry J.- CCN 323 1948-1950 (Box 33, Folder 10)
    Gillette account number: 934
  - Harris, C. P.- CCN 326 1954-1955 (Box 33, Folder 11)
    Gillette account number: 2053
  - Harris, Gibson- CCN 324 1956 (Box 33, Folder 12)
    Gillette account number: 2115
  - Harris, Hiter H., Jr.- CCN 325 1961-1962 (Box 33, Folder 13)
    Gillette account number: 2318
  - Harris, Mrs.James- CCN 327 1966-1967 (Box 33, Folder 14)
    Gillette account number: 2455
  - Harris, Reed- CCN 328 1947-1952 (Box 33, Folder 15)
    Gillette account number: 880
  - Harris, Mrs.W. A.- CCN 329 1944-1946 (Box 33, Folder 16)
  - Harrison, Mrs.Benjamin- CCN 330 1963-1964 (Box 33, Folder 17)
    Gillette account number: 2390
  - Harrison, J. Pinkey- CCN 331 1956-1957 (Box 33, Folder 18)
    Gillette account number: 474
  - Harrison, W. R., Jr.- CCN 332 1956-1958 (Box 33, Folder 19)
    Gillette account number: 2106
  - Harrisonburg High School, - CCN 333 1947 (Box 33, Folder 20)
    Gillette account number: 282
  - Hart, Mrs.G. R.- CCN 334 1956-1958 (Box 33, Folder 21)
    Gillette account number: 2099
  - Harvey, Mrs.Leo H.- CCN 335 1947-1948 (Box 33, Folder 22)
    Gillette account number: 875
  - Haskell, Howze- CCN 336 1963-1964 (Box 34, Folder 1)
  - Haskell, Dr.Lewis A.- CCN 337 1963-1964 (Box 34, Folder 2)
  - Haskins, Mrs.Robert- CCN 338 1942-1946 (Box 34, Folder 3)
    Gillette account number: 469
  - Hayes, Mrs.John G.- CCN 339 1934-1948 (Box 34, Folder 4)
    Gillette account number: 50
  - Hayes, Mrs.John G.- CCN 339 1949-1965 (Box 34, Folder 5)
  - Heaton, George D.- CCN 340 1952 (Box 34, Folder 6)
  - Hebrew Cemetery, - CCN 341 1954-1965 (Box 34, Folder 7)
    Gillette account number: 1124
  - Heindl, Thomas Armistead- CCN 342 1950-1957 (Box 34, Folder 8)
    Gillette account number: 1009
  - Heindl, Thomas Armistead- CCN 342 1959-1968 (Box 34, Folder 9)
  - Heldenfels, R. R.- CCN 343 1956 (Box 34, Folder 10)
  - Henderson, NC, Cemetery, - CCN 344 1947-1948 (Box 34, Folder 11)
  - Henley, A. B.- CCN 345 1943-1948 (Box 35, Folder 1)
    Gillette account number: 746
  - Henry, Matt- CCN 346 1958-1963 (Box 35, Folder 2)
    Gillette account number: 2238
  - Hepburn, Mrs.J. M.- CCN 347 1947 (Box 35, Folder 3)
    Gillette account number: 853
  - Hester, George F.- CCN 348 1942-1961 (Box 35, Folder 4)
  - Heusner, Mrs. A. Price- CCN 350 1954 (Box 35, Folder 5)
  - Heutte, Frederic- CCN 349 1935-1961 (Box 35, Folder 6)
  - Heyward, Mrs. Henderson- CCN 351 1954-1965 (Box 35, Folder 7)
    Gillette account number: 2433
  - Higgins, Dr.W. H.- CCN 352 1954 (Box 35, Folder 8)
    Gillette account number: 2017
  - Hill, Dr.Gladstone- CCN 353 1954 (Box 35, Folder 9)
    Gillette account number: 1189
  - Hitchcock, Mrs.Henry- CCN 354 1942-1950 (Box 35, Folder 10)
    Gillette account number: 590
  - Holderness, H. Dale- CCN 355 1950-1953 (Box 35, Folder 11)
    Gillette account number: 997
  - Hollins College, - CCN 356 1953-1957 (Box 35, Folder 12)
    Gillette account number: 1143
  - Holmes, Samuel S.- CCN 357 1943-1961 (Box 36, Folder 1)
    Gillette account number: 756
  - Holt, Miss Virginia- CCN 1057 n.d. (Box 36, Folder 2)
    Gillette account number: 2423
  - Holy Trinity Mission Seminary, - CCN 358 1964-1968 (Box 36, Folder 3)
    Gillette account number: 2453
  - Home Beneficial Insurance Company, - CCN 359 1950-1951 (Box 36, Folder 4)
    Gillette account number: 995
  - Home for the Incurable, - CCN 360 1963 (Box 36, Folder 5)
    Gillette account number: 2388
  - Hooker, Mrs.E. H.- CCN 361 1942-1944 (Box 36, Folder 6)
    Gillette account number: 398
  - Hooker, Mrs.E. H.- CCN 361 1945-1953 (Box 36, Folder 7)
  - Hooper, Mrs.Arthur U.- CCN 362 1945-1946 (Box 36, Folder 8)
    Gillette account number: 824
  - Hooper, Mrs.J. W., Jr.- CCN 363 1957 (Box 36, Folder 9)
    Gillette account number: 2185
  - Horsley, T. Braxton- CCN 364 1966 (Box 36, Folder 10)
    Gillette account number: 2180
  - Howard, Mrs.Corbett- CCN 365 1947-1951 (Box 36, Folder 11)
    Gillette account number: 858
  - Howry, Helen- CCN 366 1960 (Box 36, Folder 12)
  - Huff, C. W., Jr.- CCN 367 1948-1965 (Box 37, Folder 1)
    Gillette account number: 1104
  - Hull, Mrs. D. D.- CCN 368 1942-1943 (Box 37, Folder 2)
    Gillette account number: 736
  - Huntington Park, Inc., - CCN 369 1943-1944 (Box 37, Folder 3)
    Gillette account number: 262
  - Hunton, Eppa, IV- CCN 370 1941-1942 (Box 37, Folder 4)
    Gillette account number: 715
  - Hyde, Edwin- CCN 371 1950 (Box 37, Folder 5)
    Gillette account number: 986
  - Immanuel Baptist Church, - CCN 372 1959 (Box 37, Folder 6)
    Gillette account number: 2249
  - Indian Rock Springs, Inc., - CCN 373 1949-1960 (Box 37, Folder 7)
  - Ingles, William- CCN 374 1952-1953 (Box 37, Folder 8)
  - Ingram, William T., II- CCN 375 1963 (Box 37, Folder 9)
    Gillette account number: 2376
  - Iowa State University, - CCN 376 1942-1965 (Box 37, Folder 10)
  - Irby, Mrs. L. H.- CCN 377 1946 (Box 37, Folder 11)
  - J General, 1943-1965 (Box 37, Folder 12)
  - Jack, Mrs.H. W.- CCN 378 1965 (Box 37, Folder 13)
    Gillette account number: 2441
  - Jackson, Herbert W., Jr.- CCN 379 1942-1965 (Box 37, Folder 14)
    Gillette account number: 654
  - Jamerson, W. E.- CCN 380 1966-1967 (Box 37, Folder 15)
    Gillette account number: 2469
  - James, John Bruce, Jr.- CCN 381 1964-1965 (Box 37, Folder 16)
    Gillette account number: 2413
  - James River Scenic Expressway, - CCN 382 n.d. (Box 37, Folder 17)
  - Jamestown 4-H Camp, - CCN 383 1948-1949 (Box 37, Folder 18)
    Gillette account number: 905
  - Jamestown Pageant, - CCN 384 1947-1949 (Box 37, Folder 19)
    Gillette account number: 854
  - James - York Bank, - CCN 385 1957 (Box 37, Folder 20)
    Gillette account number: 2161
  - Jenkins, L. Howard- CCN 389 1946-1947 (Box 37, Folder 21)
    Gillette account number: 844
  - Jennings, James M.- CCN 386 1949-1950 (Box 38, Folder 1)
  - Jennings, Mrs.Page S.- CCN 387 1945 (Box 38, Folder 2)
  - Jessup, James L.- CCN 388 1962-1967 (Box 38, Folder 3)
    Gillette account number: 2362
  - Johns, Dr.Thomas- CCN 390 1962-1965 (Box 38, Folder 4)
    Gillette account number: 2342
  - Johnson, George- CCN 393 1944 (Box 38, Folder 5)
  - Johnson, Mrs.Francis L.- CCN 392 1942-1967 (Box 38, Folder 6)
    Gillette account number: 656
  - Johnson Electric Company, - CCN 391 1956 (Box 38, Folder 7)
  - Johnston County Memorial Hospital, - CCN 394 1949-1962 (Box 38, Folder 8)
    Gillette account number: 944
  - Johnston-Willis Hospital, - CCN 395 1965-1968 (Box 38, Folder 9)
    Gillette account number: 2301
  - Jones, Ann Slone- CCN 396 1957-1966 (Box 38, Folder 10)
    Gillette account number: 2332
  - Jones, Mrs.Arthur H.- CCN 397 1942-1962 (Box 38, Folder 11)
    Gillette account number: 379
  - Jones, Harold- CCN 427 1957 (Box 38, Folder 12)
  - Jones, J. D., Jr.- CCN 398 1964 (Box 38, Folder 13)
    Gillette account number: 2410
  - Jones and Robbins Real Estate, - CCN 399 1952 (Box 38, Folder 14)
    Gillette account number: 1079
  - Jones, W. Ashby, III- CCN 400 1958 (Box 38, Folder 15)
    Gillette account number: 2244
  - Jones, W. M., Jr.- CCN 401 1951-1952 (Box 38, Folder 16)
  - Jordan, Matt P.- CCN 402 1956-1957 (Box 38, Folder 17)
    Gillette account number: 2122
  - Joyner, T. Eli, Jr.- CCN 403 1951 (Box 38, Folder 18)
  - K General, 1938-1963 (Box 39, Folder 1)
  - Kallman, Mrs. Robert- CCN 404 1951-1952 (Box 39, Folder 2)
    Gillette account number: 1073
  - Kaltenbach, Mrs. Henry J.- CCN 405 1946-1951 (Box 39, Folder 3)
    Gillette account number: 568
  - Keane, Donald C.- CCN 406 1952 (Box 39, Folder 4)
  - Kearns, Amos Ragan- CCN 407 1944-1945 (Box 39, Folder 5)
  - Kelley, Mrs.I. Dee- CCN 408 1946-1950 (Box 39, Folder 6)
    Gillette account number: 815
  - Kelly, Mrs. Shaun, Jr.- CCN 409 1952 (Box 39, Folder 7)
    Gillette account number: 1109
  - Kem, James P.- CCN 410 1954 (Box 39, Folder 8)
    Gillette account number: 777
  - Kenmore, - CCN 411 1925-1930 (Box 39, Folder 9)
    Gillette account number: 221
  - Kenmore, - CCN 411 1931 Jan-Jly (Box 39, Folder 10)
  - Kenmore, - CCN 411 1931 Aug-Dec (Box 39, Folder 11)
  - Kenmore, - CCN 411 1932-1936 (Box 39, Folder 12)
  - Kenmore, - CCN 411 1937-1940 (Box 39, Folder 13)
  - Kenmore, - CCN 411 1941-1953 (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - Kenmore, - CCN 411 1954-1959 (Box 40, Folder 2)
  - Kerr Reservoir Development Commission, - CCN 412 1954-1959 (Box 40, Folder 3)
    Gillette account number: 2012
  - Kidd, Pam D.- CCN 413 1959 (Box 40, Folder 4)
  - Kilham, Mrs. Austin D.- CCN 414 1943-1960 (Box 40, Folder 5)
    Gillette account number: 700
  - Kimbrough, F. R.- CCN 415 1958 (Box 40, Folder 6)
    Gillette account number: 2242
  - King, Dr.Francis P.- CCN 416 1954-1955 (Box 40, Folder 7)
    Gillette account number: 2039
  - King, W. Johnston- CCN 417 1949-1951 (Box 40, Folder 8)
    Gillette account number: 955
  - Kings College, - CCN 418 1959 (Box 40, Folder 9)
  - Kittrell, J. B.- CCN 419 1951-1952 (Box 40, Folder 10)
    Gillette account number: 1081
  - Kjellstrom, Mrs. David- CCN 420 1963 (Box 40, Folder 11)
    Gillette account number: 1082
  - Klaus, Philip W.- CCN 421 1955-1964 (Box 40, Folder 12)
    Gillette account number: 2069
  - Knickerbocker, K. K.- CCN 423 1950-1951 (Box 40, Folder 13)
    Gillette account number: 1011
  - Knight, Floyd E.- CCN 422 1942-1960 (Box 40, Folder 14)
    Gillette account number: 246
  - Koontz, Karl- CCN 424 1954 (Box 40, Folder 15)
  - Kreuter, Jack M.- CCN 425 1963 (Box 40, Folder 16)
    Gillette account number: 2381
  - Krey, John H.- CCN 426 1952-1966 (Box 40, Folder 17)
    Gillette account number: 1085
  - L General, 1942-1965 (Box 41, Folder 1)
  - Labouisse, Mrs. John- CCN 428 1951 (Box 41, Folder 2)
  - Lafferty, Edgar F., Jr.- CCN 429 1951 (Box 41, Folder 3)